import{c as w,b as o,d as c}from"./main.810f1830.js";class b{constructor(e){this.storage=e}async load(e){return this.storage.load(e)}async save(e){return this.storage.save(e)}}class l{constructor(e){this.storage=e}async load(e){return this.storage.load(e)}async save(e){return this.storage.save(e)}}function s(a){return a.title.toLowerCase().replace(/\s/g,"-")}async function i(a,e){const t=await a.createWritable();await t.write(e),await t.close()}async function d(a){const e=new FileReader;return e.readAsText(a),await new Promise(t=>{e.onload=()=>{t(e.result)}})}const f={async load(a){const{contract:e}=JSON.parse(await d(a),(t,r)=>t==="createdAt"?new Date(r):r);return w(e).updateMetadata({savedAt:new Date(a.lastModified)})},async save(a){const e=JSON.stringify({contract:a},(t,r)=>t==="savedAt"?void 0:r);if(window.showSaveFilePicker){const t=await window.showSaveFilePicker({suggestedName:s(a),startIn:"desktop",types:[{accept:{"application/json":[".json"]}}]});await i(t,e)}else await o(()=>import("./FileSaver.min.052f6dcd.js").then(function(t){return t.F}),["assets/FileSaver.min.052f6dcd.js","assets/vendor.8502b632.js"]).then(({default:t})=>{const r=new Blob([e],{type:"application/json;charset=utf-8"});t.saveAs(r,`${s(a)}.json`)})}},S={id:"db2a1d38-01fb-4ea2-bc6f-b5213413c809",title:"EVB-IT Cloud",modules:[{id:"0b141639-8718-4ad9-9839-ec89aa8a1ec4",title:"Rubrum",steps:[{id:"06817a49-dd7b-4d8a-9c5b-77702e913a30",prompt:"Schritt 1.1",type:"TextAnswerStep",answer:{},produce:"Textbaustein: ${answer}"},{id:"c22cb3a2-2f89-47eb-b90c-a11f427ca6c8",prompt:"Schritt 1.2",type:"TextAnswerStep",answer:{}},{id:"f7e2bb12-ba14-4686-8513-afbdcab276a8",prompt:"Schritt 1.3",type:"SingleChoiceAnswerStep",answer:{choices:[{text:"Auswahl A",path:[{id:"57c97b0d-4eae-439e-b747-c297b76128e5",prompt:"Schritt 1.3 A",type:"TextAnswerStep",answer:{}}]},{text:"Auswahl B",path:[{id:"0b79fbb8-18f4-4824-af2a-3f4a95dc8cc6",prompt:"Schritt 1.3 B",type:"TextAnswerStep",answer:{}}]}]}},{id:"f7e2bb12-ba14-4686-8513-afbdcab276a8",prompt:"Schritt 1.4",type:"MultipleChoiceAnswerStep",answer:{choices:[{text:"Auswahl 1",path:[{id:"57c97b0d-4eae-439e-b747-c297b76128e5",prompt:"Schritt 1.4 1",type:"TextAnswerStep",answer:{}}]},{text:"Auswahl 2",path:[{id:"0b79fbb8-18f4-4824-af2a-3f4a95dc8cc6",prompt:"Schritt 1.4 2",type:"TextAnswerStep",answer:{}}]}]}},{id:"5ee3e9de-5052-49ac-95ed-849df72a7167",prompt:"Schritt 1.5",type:"RichTextAnswerStep",answer:{},produce:"Textbaustein: ${answer}"},{id:"5ee3e9de-5052-49ac-95ed-849df72a7167",prompt:"Schritt 1.6",type:"RichTextAnswerStep",answer:{}},{id:"c22cb3a2-2f89-47eb-b90c-a11f427ca6c8",prompt:"Schritt 1.7",type:"SheetAnswerStep",answer:{value:[{"Lfd Nr":"1","Produkt/ Leistung":"Amazon Web Services",Menge:"1",MVD:"Juni '22",Beginn:"01.01.22","Monatlicher Preis":"3989,86\u20AC"}]}}]},{id:"2407b57d-dfb2-487e-a4b2-d9f6f720cebe",title:"Gegenstand und Bestandteile des Vertrags",steps:[{id:"203e3a8f-e8c7-45b7-86e7-e6390393a348",prompt:"Schritt 2.1",type:"TextAnswerStep",answer:{}},{id:"0b570aab-fa1b-4d93-aab3-35250b8590dc",prompt:"Schritt 2.2",type:"TextAnswerStep",answer:{}},{id:"c8a04406-bba5-4968-bf2a-54122f58fbc3",prompt:"Schritt 2.3",type:"TextAnswerStep",answer:{}}]},{id:"d00fdd08-805a-4c11-8e19-c57ca770f09f",title:"Gegenstand der Leistungen",steps:[{id:"28acb64b-2c87-44c2-a112-10128a1ca546",prompt:"Schritt 3.1",type:"TextAnswerStep",answer:{}},{id:"3f460bf7-305f-4d53-a01b-074aa148c179",prompt:"Schritt 3.2",type:"TextAnswerStep",answer:{}},{id:"3cd87b83-60fa-4fd3-953b-fb0ad6d57a46",prompt:"Schritt 3.3",type:"TextAnswerStep",answer:{}},{id:"253a3dcf-9731-4537-8be3-908ec0e0c887",prompt:"Schritt 3.4",type:"TextAnswerStep",answer:{}}]}]},p=new Map,n=c(S);p.set(n.id,n);const h={findById(a){const e=p.get(a);if(typeof e=="undefined")throw new Error("Contract not found");return e}},u={async load(a){const{playbook:e}=JSON.parse(await d(a),(t,r)=>t==="createdAt"?new Date(r):r);return c(e).updateMetadata({savedAt:new Date(a.lastModified)})},async save(a){const e=JSON.stringify({playbook:a},(t,r)=>t==="savedAt"?void 0:r);if(window.showSaveFilePicker){const t=await window.showSaveFilePicker({suggestedName:s(a),startIn:"desktop",types:[{accept:{"application/json":[".json"]}}]});await i(t,e)}else await o(()=>import("./FileSaver.min.052f6dcd.js").then(function(t){return t.F}),["assets/FileSaver.min.052f6dcd.js","assets/vendor.8502b632.js"]).then(({default:t})=>{const r=new Blob([e],{type:"application/json;charset=utf-8"});t.saveAs(r,`${s(a)}.json`)})}},A=()=>h,m=()=>new b(f),g=()=>new l(u);export{A as a,g as b,m};
